Prescott S. Bush Papers
© 2005 University of Connecticut
- Series IV: Press Releases, undated, 1952-1962
  - Correspondence—New Haven Railroad trustees, 1961 August 3 (Box 12:, Folder 867)
  - Radio-TV Script of regular show, 1961 August 4 (Box 12:, Folder 868)
  - TV script—Berlin crisis, defense spending, 1961 August 4 (Box 12:, Folder 869)
  - Correspondence—New Haven Railroad trustees, 1961 August 14 (Box 12:, Folder 870)
  - Radio-TV show with John J. McCloy, 1961 August 16 (Box 12:, Folder 871)
  - “Foreign Assistance Act of 1961”, 1961 August 16 (Box 12:, Folder 872)
  - John J. McCloy—East-West Berlin Crisis; Armament and Disarmament, 1961 August 18 (Box 12:, Folder 873)
  - TV Script—John J. McCloy, 1961 August 20 (Box 12:, Folder 874)
  - Script—“Your Senator's Report—Bush, Clark and Scott”, 1961 August 20 (Box 12:, Folder 875)
  - “Exhibitions in Foreign Countries of American Production”, 1961 August 22 (Box 12:, Folder 876)
  - Schedule in CT, 1961 August 24 (Box 12:, Folder 877)
  - Foreign Assistance Act—Congressional Record, 1961 August 18 (Box 12:, Folder 878)
  - Slovak contributions to New England Culture, 1961 September 8 (Box 12:, Folder 879)
  - Berlin Crisis, Nuclear Testing, Thurmond-Fulbright Indoctrination resolution, New Haven Railroad, Inflation and Increased cost of living, 1961 September 8 (Box 12:, Folder 880)
  - Records of session, Civil Rights, Inflation, 1961 September 10 (Box 12:, Folder 881)
  - Authorization of Savings Banks to receive Federal Charters, 1961 September 11 (Box 12:, Folder 882)
  - Pittman—Assistant Secretary of Defense for Civil Defense, 1961 September 15 (Box 12:, Folder 883)
  - Rule XXII, 1961 September 15 (Box 12:, Folder 884)
  - World Bank and International Monetary Fund Conferences, 1961 September 15 (Box 12:, Folder 885)
  - President's speech—Lasting peace, survival of the World before the U.N., 1961 September 26 (Box 12:, Folder 886)
  - Weekend schedule, 1961 September 27 (Box 12:, Folder 887)
  - CT schedule, 1961 October 5 (Box 12:, Folder 888)
  - “Pulaski Day 1961” excerpts from remarks, 1961 October 9 (Box 12:, Folder 889)
  - Columbus day—excerpts from remarks, 1961 October 9 (Box 12:, Folder 890)
  - Schedule, 1961 October 13 (Box 12:, Folder 891)
  - Correspondence—Foreign aid and economic development, 1961 October 14 (Box 12:, Folder 892)
  - Dedication of Jonathon Law High School, Milford, CT, 1961 October 16 (Box 12:, Folder 893)
  - Excerpts of remarks—urban renewal, 1961 October 20 (Box 12:, Folder 894)
  - CT schedule, 1961 October 20 (Box 12:, Folder 895)
  - Schedule, 1961 October 27 (Box 12:, Folder 896)
  - Schedule, 1961 November 3 (Box 12:, Folder 897)
  - American Education Week—student assembly Stamford, CT, 1961 November 9 (Box 12:, Folder 898)
  - Schedule, 1961 November 10 (Box 12:, Folder 899)
  - Hearing of Senate's Special Committee on Aging, 1961 November 16 (Box 12:, Folder 900)
  - “What's Ahead for America”—CT Chamber of Commerce, 1961 November 22 (Box 12:, Folder 901)
  - Editorials, 1961 November 24, 27 (Box 12:, Folder 902)
  - Newsletter, 1961 December 1 (Box 12:, Folder 903)
  - Opening of hearings by the Joint Economic Committee, Subcommittee on Foreign Economic policy, 1961 December 4 (Box 12:, Folder 904)
  - Subcommittee on Foreign Economic policy, 1961 December 6 (Box 12:, Folder 905)
  - Schedule, 1961 December 8 (Box 12:, Folder 906)
  - Schedule, 1961 December 15 (Box 12:, Folder 907)
  - Broader executive power over tariffs—“A” release, 1962 January 7 (Box 12:, Folder 908)
  - Broader executive power over tariffs—“B” release, 1962 January 7 (Box 12:, Folder 909)
  - Curtis report of Individual views on broader executive power over tariffs, 1962 January 7 (Box 12:, Folder 910)
  - State of the Union message, 1962 January 11 (Box 12:, Folder 911)
  - Report of the Joint Economic Committee, 1962 January 17 (Box 12:, Folder 912)
  - President's Budget message, 1962 January 18 (Box 12:, Folder 913)
  - Foreign policy, Congo, Domestic issues, Tariff, Trade, Tax, 1962 January 19 (Box 12:, Folder 914)
  - S. 500 to reimburse states for free and toll highways, 1962 January 22 (Box 12:, Folder 915)
  - S. 2666; Tax relief; Older people, 1962 January 25 (Box 12:, Folder 916)
  - S. 2740 Restricting Communist propaganda in the Mails, 1962 January 25 (Box 12:, Folder 917)
  - Administration's Trade policy, 1962 January 25 (Box 12:, Folder 918)
  - Academy nominations, 1962 February 1 (Box 12:, Folder 919)
  - Tax relief for New Haven Railroad, 1962 February 1 (Box 12:, Folder 920)
  - Department of Urban Affairs Housing, New Haven Railroad, Trade proposals, 1962 February 2 (Box 12:, Folder 921)
  - Lincoln Day speech schedule, 1962 February 7 (Box 12:, Folder 922)
  - Unemployment—Federal spending, 1962 February 10 (Box 12:, Folder 923)
  - Unemployment; Federal spending; tariffs; tax reform, 1962 February 11 (Box 12:, Folder 924)
  - H.R. 9990—Trade bill, 1962 February 12 (Box 12:, Folder 925)
  - Hartford Rotary Club—expanding budget, balance of payment deficit, tariffs and trade, 1962 February 12 (Box 12:, Folder 926)
  - Speech—Republican Town Committee, European Common market, trade negotiations, 1962 February 13 (Box 12:, Folder 927)
  - Trade program, balance of payments deficit, 1962 February 14 (Box 12:, Folder 928)
  - Testimonial—William Bertini, Administration's Trade bill, tariff, 1962 February 15 (Box 12:, Folder 929)
  - Keating—Special powers reduce taxes; public works programs, 1962 February 16 (Box 12:, Folder 930)
  - Correspondence—New Haven Railroad, 1962 February 19 (Box 12:, Folder 931)
  - President's reorganization plan—Urban affairs, 1962 February 20 (Box 12:, Folder 932)
  - Newsletter, 1962 March 1 (Box 13:, Folder 933)
  - Republican views on President's economic report, 1962 March 3 (Box 13:, Folder 934)
  - Omnibus Tax bill, Tax depreciation policy, withholding, 1962 March 3 (Box 13:, Folder 935)
  - Kennedy's challenge to Krushchev—disarmament, 1962 March 3 (Box 13:, Folder 936)
  - Annual report of the Joint Economic Committee, 1962 March 6 (Box 13:, Folder 937)
  - Minority views of annual report, 1962 March 8 (Box 13:, Folder 938)
  - Department of Commerce's misleading statistics, employment generated by foreign trade, 1962 March 11 (Box 13:, Folder 939)
  - Civil Rights legislation, unemployment problems, 1962 March 16 (Box 13:, Folder 940)
  - Latin American Affairs, 1962 March 30 (Box 13:, Folder 941)
  - Joint Economic Committee, 1962 April 2 (Box 13:, Folder 942)
  - Unemployment, 1962 April 2 (Box 13:, Folder 943)
  - Unemployment and Job discrimination, 1962 April 2 (Box 13:, Folder 944)
  - Proposed “realignment” of 43rd Infantry Division, 1962 April 5 (Box 13:, Folder 945)
  - National Economy; Unemployment, 1962 April 6 (Box 13:, Folder 946)
  - Speech—Col. Glenn Flight, Space Information exchange with Soviets, 1962 April 8 (Box 13:, Folder 947)
  - Editorial, 1962 April 8 (Box 13:, Folder 948)
  - Unemployment; $600 million Public Works bill; Trade Program and effects on unemployment, 1962 April 13 (Box 13:, Folder 949)
  - Amendments to H.R. 10904, Labor HEW appropriations, 1962 April 17 (Box 13:, Folder 950)
  - Speech—20% withholding on interest and dividends, 1962 April 18 (Box 13:, Folder 951)
  - S. 3217—Unemployment, 1962 April 25 (Box 13:, Folder 952)
  - S. 3217—Technical Education Act of 1962, 1962 April 25 (Box 13:, Folder 953)
  - CT schedule, 1962 April 25 (Box 13:, Folder 954)
  - Tax on interest dividends; literacy test legislation; Unemployment, 1962 April 27 (Box 13:, Folder 955)
  - Trade program and tariff-cutting, 1962 April 28 (Box 13:, Folder 956)
  - Speech—“Elite clique of Inner Circle White House Advisors”, 1962 April 28 (Box 13:, Folder 957)
  - Speech—Polaris, Navy League, 1962 April 30 (Box 13:, Folder 958)
  - Address—Failure in closing the job gap, 1962 April 30 (Box 13:, Folder 959)
  - Speech—Nuclear testing resumption and National Security, 1962 April 30 (Box 13:, Folder 960)
  - Newsletter, 1962 May 1 (Box 13:, Folder 961)
  - Speech—Federal loans to Parochial and Other non-profit schools, 1962 May 1 (Box 13:, Folder 962)
  - Speech—Boss rule in state, debt and tax increases, 1962 May 1 (Box 13:, Folder 963)
  - S. 2996, Joint Economic Committee and US Balance of payments problem, 1962 May 3 (Box 13:, Folder 964)
  - “The US Balance of Payments deficit: Realism needed not rose-colored glasses”, 1962 May 3 (Box 13:, Folder 965)
  - CT schedule, 1962 May 3 (Box 13:, Folder 966)
  - Poland's Constitution Day—171st Anniversary, 1962 May 3 (Box 13:, Folder 967)
  - Speech—Commemoration of Polish Constitution, 1962 May 4 (Box 13:, Folder 968)
  - Speech—Tribute to Mayor Meskill and republican workers, 1962 May 6 (Box 13:, Folder 969)
  - Speech—American diplomacy, negotiations with Communist nations, 1962 May 6 (Box 13:, Folder 970)
  - “Tariff debate involves more than just Trade or Fade”, 1962 May 6 (Box 13:, Folder 971)
  - Medicare, 1962 May 7 (Box 13:, Folder 972)
  - “Job Gap”, 1962 May 10 (Box 13:, Folder 973)
  - Withholding tax on interest and dividends; Public works bill, 1962 May 11 (Box 13:, Folder 974)
  - Public Works appropriations; Unemployment; Withholding on Interest; Trade expansion bill, 1962 May 13 (Box 13:, Folder 975)
  - “I Shall not be a Candidate for Re-election”, 1962 May 16 (Box 13:, Folder 976)
  - S.J. Res. 85 Congressional representation for D.C., 1962 May 23 (Box 13:, Folder 977)
  - Tax bill, Health care for the Aged, Withholding tax, 1962 May 25 (Box 13:, Folder 978)
  - Retirement announcement, 1962 June 14 (Box 13:, Folder 979)
  - H.R. 1006 Public welfare amendments of 1962, 1962 June 27 (Box 13:, Folder 980)
  - Open hearings on state of the economy, 1962 June 27 (Box 13:, Folder 981)
  - National Debt limit, 1962 June 28 (Box 13:, Folder 982)
  - Stockpiling and Naval reserves, 1962 June 29 (Box 13:, Folder 983)
  - Amendments to H.R. 11970, proposed trade expansion act of 1962, 1962 August 2 (Box 13:, Folder 984)
  - Amendments to Trade bill H.R. 11970, 1962 August 2 (Box 13:, Folder 985)
  - Urban Mass Transportation Act of 1962, 1962 August 8 (Box 13:, Folder 986)
  - Amendments to H.R. 11970, 1962 August 13 (Box 13:, Folder 987)
  - Correspondence—Amendments to H.R. 11970, 1962 August 17 (Box 13:, Folder 988)
  - Tribute to Senator Dirksen, 1962 August 22 (Box 13:, Folder 989)
  - President's request for standby authority to call Reserves (Cuba), 1962 September 7 (Box 13:, Folder 990)
  - Amendment to S.J. Res. 224 Standby authority, 1962 September 12 (Box 13:, Folder 991)
  - H.R. 30 Northeastern Water and Related Land Resources Compact, 1962 September 18 (Box 13:, Folder 992)
  - Academy Appointments, 1962 December 15 (Box 13:, Folder 993)
  - Speech—Liberation of Communist bloc nations, undated (Box 13:, Folder 994)
  - Address—“Our American Republic: What it Means”, undated (Box 13:, Folder 995)
- Series V: Speeches 1953-1962
  - Lincoln Day—New Haven, 1953 February 12 (Box 14:, Folder 996)
  - League of Republican Women of the District of Columbia [D.C. representation], 1953 March 2 (Box 14:, Folder 997)
  - American League CT Rehabilitation Commission, 1953 March 4 (Box 14:, Folder 998)
  - Yale Club of Washington, 1953 April 7 (Box 14:, Folder 999)
  - Waterbury Chamber of Commerce, 1953 April 11 (Box 14:, Folder 1000)
  - Bond Club of New York “Sound Dollar and debt management”, 1953 July 2 (Box 14:, Folder 1001)
  - Rotary Club of Greenwich, 1953 August 12 (Box 14:, Folder 1002)
  - High School meetings “Our American Republic: What it means to Us”, 1953 Fall (Box 14:, Folder 1003)
  - Danbury-Farmington, 1953 September 18 (Box 14:, Folder 1004)
  - Clock Manufacturing Association of America, 1953 September 18 (Box 14:, Folder 1005)
  - Steuben Society of America, 1953 September 26 (Box 14:, Folder 1006)
  - American Life Convention, 1953 October 9 (Box 14:, Folder 1007)
  - Savings Banks' Association 51st annual Convention, 1953 October 13 (Box 14:, Folder 1008)
  - United Nation's Day—Greenwich, 1953 October 23 (Box 14:, Folder 1009)
  - New Haven County Republicans, 1954 January 21 (Box 14:, Folder 1010)
  - Lincoln Day—Waterbury, 1954 February 12 (Box 14:, Folder 1011)
  - Report on Foreign Economic policy, 1954 February 23 (Box 14:, Folder 1012)
  - University Club, 1954 March 13 (Box 14:, Folder 1013)
  - Monetary policy, 1954 April 22 (Box 14:, Folder 1014)
  - Hartford Foreign Policy Association “American Foreign Policy in the 'Age of Peril' ”, 1954 October 11 (Box 14:, Folder 1015)
  - Kiwanis Club of Waterbury—“Security Risks”, 1954 October 13 (Box 14:, Folder 1016)
  - CT Federation of Labor, 69th Annual Convention, 1954 October 14 (Box 14:, Folder 1017)
  - Young Republicans Club of Yale Law School and Yale College, 1954 October 26 (Box 14:, Folder 1018)
  - Sea Girt, New Jersey—speech for Clifford Case, 1954 October 28 (Box 14:, Folder 1019)
  - Naturalization Ceremonies—Bridgeport, 1954 November 11 (Box 14:, Folder 1020)
  - Lincoln Day—Glastonbury, 1955 February 10 (Box 14:, Folder 1021)
  - Lincoln Day—Manchester, 1955 February 13 (Box 14:, Folder 1022)
  - Brotherhood Week, 1955 February 20 (Box 14:, Folder 1023)
  - Birth of Nathan Hale, 200th Anniversary—New London, 1955 June 6 (Box 15:, Folder 1024)
  - Cromwell Republican Town Committee, 1955 June 6 (Box 15:, Folder 1025)
  - Cornwell Bridge High School graduation, 1955 June 17 (Box 15:, Folder 1026)
  - Veterans of Foreign Wars, 35th Annual encampment, 1955 June 19 (Box 15:, Folder 1027)
  - Marine Corps League, 1955 June 25 (Box 15:, Folder 1028)
  - Back to God program, 1955 July 10 (Box 15:, Folder 1029)
  - American Russian Festival—Stratford, 1955 August 1 (Box 15:, Folder 1030)
  - Albanian American National Organization—Bridgeport, 1955 August 7 (Box 15:, Folder 1031)
  - Liberalization of 1955, SBA loans, 1955 September 9 (Box 15:, Folder 1032)
  - Republican Club—Hartford, Flood and Party, 1955 September 13 (Box 15:, Folder 1033)
  - Labor-Management Citizen's Committee of Stamford and Greenwich Fall Conference—Highway, 1955 October 4 (Box 15:, Folder 1034)
  - University of CT, Storrs—Flood and Public service, 1955 October 4 (Box 15:, Folder 1035)
  - Investment Bankers—Hartford, 1955 October 6 (Box 15:, Folder 1036)
  - Westover School Alumnae, 1955 October 12 (Box 15:, Folder 1037)
  - Fairfield County Republican Women's Association—Report to Voters [Flood], 1955 October 26 (Box 15:, Folder 1038)
  - Middletown League of Women Voters—NIKE, 1955 October 28 (Box 15:, Folder 1039)
  - Naugatuck Valley Industrial Council—Commerce Secretary Weeks, 1955 October 31 (Box 15:, Folder 1040)
  - New Britain Foremen's Club, 1955 November 28 (Box 15:, Folder 1041)
  - CT Cancer Society, 1956 March 28 (Box 15:, Folder 1042)
  - Hartford Rotary Club—Federally Assisted Urban renewal programs, Federal flood insurance, 1956 April 16 (Box 15:, Folder 1043)
  - Sobeloff, Civil Rights, Seniority, 1956 April 24 (Box 15:, Folder 1044)
  - New Haven State Teacher's College, 1956 May 27 (Box 15:, Folder 1045)
  - Traffic Club of Eastern CT—Southern Democrats Opposition, 1956 June 12 (Box 15:, Folder 1046)
  - Republican Convention Acceptance, 1956 June 19 (Box 15:, Folder 1047)
  - Waterbury Chamber of Commerce, 1956 September 14 (Box 15:, Folder 1048)
  - League of Women Voters of CT, 1956 September 19 (Box 15:, Folder 1049)
  - Columbian Republican League, 1956 September 24 (Box 15:, Folder 1050)
  - Women's National Republican Club, 1956 September 25 (Box 15:, Folder 1051)
  - CT Federation of Labor, 1956 September 26 (Box 15:, Folder 1052)
  - Meeting in W. Hartford, 1956 September 26 (Box 15:, Folder 1053)
  - 28th Statement Senatorial district, 1956 September 27 (Box 15:, Folder 1054)
  - Middletown and North Branford, 1956 September 30 (Box 15:, Folder 1055)
  - National Republican Club, 1956 October 2 (Box 15:, Folder 1056)
  - National Council of Jewish Women, 1956 October 3 (Box 15:, Folder 1057)
  - Tolland County and Rockville Women's Republicans Club—Citizen's for Eisenhower, 1956 October 8 (Box 15:, Folder 1058)
  - Lincoln Day—Waterbury Republican Town Committee, 1957 February 9 (Box 15:, Folder 1059)
  - Sons of the American Revolution, 1957 April 3 (Box 15:, Folder 1060)
  - New England Conference of the State Federations of Women's Clubs, 1957 September 10 (Box 15:, Folder 1061)
  - Hartford and Greenwich—“The Meaning of the Sputniks”, 1957 September/December (Box 15:, Folder 1062)
  - Hartford Insurance meeting—S. 1168 SEC, 1958 January 20 (Box 16:, Folder 1063)
  - Democratic Advisors Council—Wethersfield, 1958 February (Box 16:, Folder 1064)
  - CT College for Women—Foreign Trade and Aid, 1958 February 10 (Box 16:, Folder 1065)
  - East Hartford Rotary Club, 1958 February 12 (Box 16:, Folder 1066)
  - St. Louis Speech—Education, 1958 February 23 (Box 16:, Folder 1067)
  - National Citizens Council for Better Schools, North Atlantic Region, 1958 April 21 (Box 16:, Folder 1068)
  - Student Legal Forum, University of Virginia, 1958 April 30 (Box 16:, Folder 1069)
  - National Association for Retarded Children, Northeast Region, 1958 June 7 (Box 16:, Folder 1070)
  - University of Bridgeport Commencement, 1958 June 8 (Box 16:, Folder 1071)
  - CT College for Women; Yale Alumni Donation Information, 1958 (Box 16:, Folder 1072)
  - Home Builders Association of Fairfield County—Inflation and Interest Rates, 1958 September 27 (Box 16:, Folder 1073)
  - Milford Jewish Center, 10th Anniversary, 1958 September 27 (Box 16:, Folder 1074)
  - American Assembly—“Monetary Politics”, 1958 October 17 (Box 16:, Folder 1075)
  - Testimonial—Ted Blair, 1958 October 20 (Box 16:, Folder 1076)
  - Speech—for Senator Bricker, 1958 October 22 (Box 16:, Folder 1077)
  - Bridgeport Chamber of Commerce, 1959 January 26 (Box 16:, Folder 1078)
  - League of Women Voters, 1959 February 4 (Box 16:, Folder 1079)
  - Lincoln Day, 1959 February 9 (Box 16:, Folder 1080)
  - National Cathedral Association; Sulgrave Club, 1959 April 22 (Box 16:, Folder 1081)
  - Center Church, New Haven, 1959 April 26 (Box 16:, Folder 1082)
  - Georgetown University Law Day, 1959 May 1 (Box 16:, Folder 1083)
  - New Hampshire Council on World Affairs, 1959 May 2 (Box 16:, Folder 1084)
  - Gaylord Farms Sanitorium, Wallingford, 1959 May 16 (Box 16:, Folder 1085-86)
  - US Senator Golf Dinner, 1959 June 3 (Box 16:, Folder 1087)
  - St. George's Prep School, 1959 June 11 (Box 17:, Folder 1088)
  - Inflation Seminar—Stamford, 1959 Summer (Box 17:, Folder 1089)
  - Reader's Digest, 1959 July (Box 17:, Folder 1090)
  - Torrington rededication—Bush-McCormack project, 1959 August 20 (Box 17:, Folder 1091)
  - Speech material, general outline, 1959 Fall (Box 17:, Folder 1092)
  - CT Editorial Association and ABA, 1959 Fall (Box 17:, Folder 1093)
  - CT Association for Retarded Children, 1959 September 25 (Box 17:, Folder 1094)
  - Lakeville, Hartford, Middletown, 1959 October (Box 17:, Folder 1095)
  - Pulaski Day Ceremonies, 1959 October 4 (Box 17:, Folder 1096)
  - Life Insurance Association, 1959 December 4 (Box 17:, Folder 1097)
  - Far East policy, 1959 December 19 (Box 17:, Folder 1098)
  - Dr. Dooley, 1960 January 15 (Box 17:, Folder 1099)
  - “Dinner with Ike”, 1960 January 27 (Box 17:, Folder 1100)
  - Lincoln Day—Albany, Bozrah, Seymour, Hartford, 1960 February (Box 17:, Folder 1101)
  - Senator Theodore F. Green, 1960 April 25 (Box 17:, Folder 1102)
  - Mortgage Banker's Association of America—“Politics and Housing”, 1960 May 2 (Box 17:, Folder 1103)
  - New York Chamber of Commerce—“Politics is Your Business”, 1960 May 5 (Box 17:, Folder 1104)
  - “The Party of Responsibility”, 1960 May 21 (Box 17:, Folder 1105)
  - Republican State Convention, 1960 June 6 (Box 17:, Folder 1106)
  - New London Veterans of Foreign Wars, 1960 September (Box 17:, Folder 1107)
  - “The Candidates and Issues of the 1960 Campaign”, 1960 September 1 (Box 17:, Folder 1108)
  - CT Daily Newspaper Editors—“War or Peace”, “Domestic Prosperity”, 1960 September 22 (Box 17:, Folder 1109)
  - Republican National Committee, 1960 September 9 (Box 17:, Folder 1110)
  - H.R. 10 Self-Employed Individuals Tax Retirement Act of 1960 and Medicare, 1960 October 3 (Box 18:, Folder 1111)
  - Clergymen—Hartford, 1960 October 6 (Box 18:, Folder 1112)
  - Veterans of World War I, USA, Inc., 1960 October 11 (Box 18:, Folder 1113)
  - Trade Relations Council, 1960 October 26 (Box 18:, Folder 1114)
  - Testimonial—Dominick Cocco, 1961 February 12 (Box 18:, Folder 1115)
  - Republican State Central Committee, 1961 February 14 (Box 18:, Folder 1116)
  - CT Junior Chamber of Commerce—Norwich, 1961 March 11 (Box 18:, Folder 1117)
  - University of Bridgeport, 1961 April 24 (Box 18:, Folder 1118)
  - Mutual Savings Bank Association, 1961 May 2 (Box 18:, Folder 1119)
  - Anti-Segregation Amendment to the Education Bill, 1961 May 19 (Box 18:, Folder 1120)
  - Peter Mariani, 1961 May 20 (Box 18:, Folder 1121)
  - Memorial Day Address—Bridgeport, 1961 May 30 (Box 18:, Folder 1122)
  - Greenwich High School Chorus, 1961 June 18 (Box 18:, Folder 1123)
  - Wheeler High School Graduation, North Stonington, 1961 June 22 (Box 18:, Folder 1124)
  - Norwalk, CT, 1961 October (Box 18:, Folder 1125)
  - Pulaski Day Parade, 1961 October 8 (Box 18:, Folder 1126)
  - Columbus Day, 1961 October 8 (Box 18:, Folder 1127)
  - Dedication—Jonathon Law High School, 1961 October 15 (Box 18:, Folder 1128)
  - Henry H. Townshend, Jr.—New Haven, 1961 October 19 (Box 18:, Folder 1129)
  - J.M. Wright Technical School “Vocational Technical Education”, 1961 November 9 (Box 18:, Folder 1130)
  - CT Chamber of Commerce “What's Ahead for America”, 1961 November 21 (Box 18:, Folder 1131)
  - CBS Radio—“Capital Cloakroom” Urban Affairs, 1962 February 8 (Box 18:, Folder 1132)
  - Young Republicans Club, Fairfield, 1962 February 21 (Box 18:, Folder 1133)
  - Greenwich, CT, 1962 March 6 (Box 18:, Folder 1134)
  - Litchfield County Republican Group, 1962 April 7 (Box 18:, Folder 1135)
  - Probus Clubs and Amity Clubs of New Haven, 1962 April 17 (Box 18:, Folder 1136)
  - Guilford Chamber of Commerce, 1962 April 27 (Box 18:, Folder 1137)
  - Yale Law School Forum, 1962 April 28 (Box 18:, Folder 1138)
  - Political Science Association of Hartford, 1962 April 30 (Box 19:, Folder 1139)
  - Women's Republican Club of Hartford, 1962 May 1 (Box 19:, Folder 1140)
  - American Field Service, CT Youth Forum, 1962 May 5 (Box 19:, Folder 1141)
  - Thomas J. Meskill—New Britain, 1962 May 5 (Box 19:, Folder 1142)
  - CT Public Expenditures Council, 1962 May 22 (Box 19:, Folder 1143)
  - Dedication—Low Rent Housing for Elderly, Greenwich, 1962 June 15 (Box 19:, Folder 1144)
  - NBC—“A Moment with...”, 1962 June 21 (Box 19:, Folder 1145)
  - Interview script, 1962 November (Box 19:, Folder 1146)
- Series VI: Photographs and Films, undated, 1955-1962
  - Prescott Bush (Official), undated (Box 20:, Folder 1147)
  - Flood, 1955 (Box 20:, Folder 1148)
  - Winsted, CT flood, 1955 (Box 20:, Folder 1149)
  - Flood, 1955 (Box 20:, Folder 1150-1152)
  - TV shows, 1956-1957; (2 reels) (Box 21)
  - TV shows, 1958; (4 reels)
  - TV shows, education, 1958
  - Senate programs, 1959; (2 reels)
  - Senate programs, 1960; (2 reels) (Box 22)
  - TV, Multiple Sclerosis spot, 1961
  - TV, “Your Senator's Report”, 1961
  - Scripts, 1960-1961
  - Unknown film, 1962 (Box 23)
  - TV, WTIC, 1962 January 21
  - TV, WTIC, 1962 February 4
  - TV, WHCT, 1962 February
  - TV, WTIC, 1962 February
  - TV, WNHC, 1962 February
  - Scripts
  - TV, WNHC, 1962 March
  - TV, WHCT, 1962 March
  - TV, WHNB, 1962 April
  - TV, WNHC, 1962 April (Box 24)
  - TV, WNHC, 1962 April
  - TV, WNHC, 1962 May
  - TV, WNHC, 1962 May
  - Scripts
  - Bush, Frank Mazzabuffi, Lawrence Gilman—Republican State Convention, 1962 June
  - TV, WHNB
  - TV, WHNB, 1962 March
  - TV, WHNB, 1962 March
  - TV, WHNB, 1962 March
  - TV, WNHC, 1962 April